{"items": [{"question": "incapable of being tired", "answer": "indefatigable", "options": ["perspicacious", "magnanimous", "indefatigable", "ingenuous"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "inability to mask your feelings", "answer": "ingenuous", "options": ["versatile", "perspicacious", "ingenuous", "magnanimous"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "having keen mental sensing and understanding", "answer": "perspicacious", "options": ["magnanimous", "stoical", "versatile", "perspicacious"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "generous in forgiving an insult or injury", "answer": "magnanimous", "options": ["magnanimous", "stoical", "versatile", "intrepid"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "capable of turning easily from one task to another", "answer": "versatile", "options": ["stoical", "versatile", "intrepid", "scintillating"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Seeming unaffected by pleasure or pain", "answer": "stoical", "options": ["urbane", "scintillating", "intrepid", "stoical"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "untouchable to fear or intimidation", "answer": "intrepid", "options": ["urbane", "convivial", "scintillating", "intrepid"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Having brief brilliant points or flashes of light", "answer": "scintillating", "options": ["vivacious", "urbane", "scintillating", "convivial"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "having the polish as regarded as social life in major cities", "answer": "urbane", "options": ["vivacious", "convivial", "urbane", "vivid"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "friendly, agreeable", "answer": "convivial", "options": ["convivial", "revive", "vivid", "vivacious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "lively and animated", "answer": "vivacious", "options": ["vivid", "revive", "vivacious", "vivisection"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "strikingly bright or intense as color, light etc.", "answer": "vivid", "options": ["vivisection", "revive", "viviparous", "vivid"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "take up again; set in motion", "answer": "revive", "options": ["oviparous", "vivisection", "viviparous", "revive"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "The act of cutting into a living body", "answer": "vivisection", "options": ["vivisection", "viviparous", "ovulate", "oviparous"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "one who is bringing fourth living young rather than eggs", "answer": "viviparous", "options": ["ovulate", "viviparous", "oviparous", "vital"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "one producing eggs that mature and hatch after being expelled from the body", "answer": "oviparous", "options": ["vital", "oviparous", "ovulate", "revitalize"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Produce and discharge eggs", "answer": "ovulate", "options": ["defrost", "revitalize", "vital", "ovulate"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "be relevant to life", "answer": "vital", "options": ["vital", "defrost", "decompose", "revitalize"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "to give new life to", "answer": "revitalize", "options": ["declassify", "revitalize", "defrost", "decompose"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "to remove the ice from", "answer": "defrost", "options": ["decompose", "vitamin", "declassify", "defrost"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "to separate into elements", "answer": "decompose", "options": ["devitalize", "declassify", "decompose", "vitamin"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "to remove the classification from information that restricts the access in terms of secrecy", "answer": "declassify", "options": ["bon-vivant", "declassify", "vitamin", "devitalize"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Any of a group of organic substances essential in small quantities to normal metabolism", "answer": "vitamin", "options": ["vitamin", "gourmet", "devitalize", "bon-vivant"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "make lifeless or weaken", "answer": "devitalize", "options": ["bon-vivant", "gourmet", "devitalize", "gourmand"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A person who enjoys luxuries especially good food and drinks", "answer": "bon-vivant", "options": ["glutton", "bon-vivant", "gourmand", "gourmet"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "a connoisseur of fine food and drinks", "answer": "gourmet", "options": ["indefatigable", "glutton", "gourmet", "gourmand"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "one who is fond of good eating and to excess", "answer": "gourmand", "options": ["ingenuous", "gourmand", "glutton", "indefatigable"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "one who eats and drinks excessively or viraciously", "answer": "glutton", "options": ["indefatigable", "perspicacious", "glutton", "ingenuous"], "answer_index": 3}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 32 to 33.txt", "total": 28}